Vadim Buryakovsky vadimburyakovsky@gmail.com 267-274-7406

Summary: I am a software developer seeking a position as a MERN stack developer or .NET C# developer. I have a Master's degree in Computer Science from Drexel University. I have 4 years of work experience using .NET C# and ASP.NET MVC which included 3 years of creating and maintaining a small business website. Due to a recent gap in employment and to refresh my web development skills I recently completed the UPenn LPS Coding Bootcamp where I learned Mongodb, Express, React, and Node, including lots of use of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery and Bootstrap.

Work History

9/2017 - 8/2020

Unemployed due to health issues

- UPenn LPS Coding Bootcamp 05/2020
- Self study of .NET
 - o MVC, WCF, Entity Framework
- Self study of web development; HTML/CSS/JavaScript.
- Self study of academic areas of computer science to potentially enroll in a Phd Computer Science program in the future.
 - Data Structures and Algorithms
 - Networking
 - Logic for proving program correctness
 - o Artificial Intelligence

PrimePay 03/2017 - 09/2017

Junior Software Developer.

- Developed tax software which generated electronic tax files and electronic tax forms using C# and Microsoft SQL.
- Wrote SQL queries to move data from databases to the e-files and forms.
 - o Involved writing SQL code which populated dozens of tabular fields on the form in the correct X,Y position.
- Created file templates using line position to move data to the correct place in the electronic tax files.
- Wrote unit tests to guarantee correctness of code.

proServices 09/2015 - 12/2015

Software Developer

- Developed database software using NHibernate.
- Replaced ADO.Net code with NHibernate code for storing and retrieving data.

proServices 07/2012 - 08/2012

Software Development Internship

• Developed networking software using C# Windows Communication Foundation

• Wrote program to move large amounts of data efficiently between workstations.

EasySoldAuction 2002 – 2012

Customer Service Associate and Web Developer

Developed public facing website using .NET MVC

- Functionality of the website was to allow customers to keep track of items that they gave to the store to sell on their behalf.
- Used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create front end of the website.
 - Created forms for customers to submit inquiries and to create customer accounts.
 - Customer accounts were used to check status of customer items
- Used MVC for backend of the website.
- Used Microsoft SQL Server to store customer's account information and item status.
 - o Used Entity Framework for C# database coding.

Education

University of Pennsylvania LPS Coding Bootcamp

Certificate 05/2020

- MERN (Mongdb, Express, React, Node. js) Stack
- Bootstrap
- MySQL
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Drexel University Philadelphia, PA

Master's degree in Computer Science 2016

Temple University Philadelphia, PA

Bachelor's degree in Geography and Urban Studies

Skills

- .NET
 - o C#
 - o MVC
 - o Entity Framework
 - Windows Communication Foundation
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- React
- Node.js

- ExpressMongodbMySQL
- Microsoft SQL Server